The actual bits of punctuation and
grammar that you need to know are
very few, and you can look
them up on the internet.
Word processors will help
you out with a lot of it.
There are other programs
like Grammarly, and
this is one of the few uses of
AI that I think is genuinely useful, is
that you can drop a bunch of text that
you've written into it and say, have
I made any really serious mistakes?
And it will mention some things, and
then you can decide whether you want to
fix them or not. Basically,
the reason I've written
split infinitive is, split
infinitive is an example of something
that somebody has decided to make a
point of, which is a thing in Latin,
but isn't a thing in English.
So the famous example is to boldly go.
To boldly go is fine in English.
It's impossible in Latin because
the infinitive is just one word,
but somebody
was making a point about this, and
those people are dicks, mainly.